{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "a day\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "days",
      "explain": "\n\n- day -> days\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pig\n\n---> ten ___",
      "answer": "pigs",
      "explain": "\n\n- pig -> pigs",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a joy\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "joys",
      "explain": "\n\n- joy -> joys\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lion\n\n---> seven ___",
      "answer": "lions",
      "explain": "\n\n- lion -> lions",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a church\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "churches",
      "explain": "\n\n- church -> churches\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hen\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "hens",
      "explain": "\n\n- hen -> hens",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pony \n\n---> three  ___ ",
      "answer": "ponies",
      "explain": "\n\n- pony -> ponies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fox \n\n---> nine ___ ",
      "answer": "foxes",
      "explain": "\n\n- fox -> foxes\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman \n\n---> ten ___ ",
      "answer": "women",
      "explain": "\n\n- woman -> women\n(irregular plural)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "an injury\n\n---> eight ___",
      "answer": "injuries",
      "explain": "\n\n- injury -> injuries\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}